globalbx.com 2004-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Businesses for sale at GlobalBX - Business for Sale, Business Brokers, Franchise Businesses

| **OUR MISSION**  
---  
  
Our mission is to provide a free confidential forum to facilitate the buying and selling of businesses, and to be the complete business source for helping business buyers and business sellers through the business exchange process.  

**FEATURED LISTINGS**  
---  
* Bar in San Francisco \- This is one of hottest bars in the San Francisco Bay Area. It is completely packed on ...* Fast Food Restaurant \- Fabulous, One Of A Kind Business. Features Deli, Sandwiches, Meats, ...* Coin Laundry \- Busy Coin Laundry In Great Location. New Apartment Complex Development across the ...  

**PRIVACY POLICY**

At GlobalBX™, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our users. This policy was developed to promote trust and confidence in our Site. GlobalBX™ is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of third party websites to which www.globalbx.com may link. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information we collect on the GlobalBX™ website (the "Site"), and would not apply to information we collect in any other fashion. By using this Site, you agree to the terms of the GlobalBX™ Privacy Policy. GlobalBX™ reserves the right to change, modify, or update this statement at any time without notice.

**Collecting your Personal Information**

In general, you can visit our Site without divulging any personal information. Information is gathered when you choose to become a Registered User. As a Registered User, you could list a business for sale, express interest in a business listing, and use materials and other services on the Site. The information allows us to provide users with private and secure areas to post and modify their original content on our Site. We will request personal information from you such as your name, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, as well as information about your business for sale. We collect personal information from users on a voluntary basis only. Your personal information will not be shared unless you choose to disclose it or otherwise as set forth in this Privacy Policy. All information provided by you will be stored in a secure manner. 

Please keep in mind that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of GlobalBX™ such as in our business exchange or message boards, such information may be collected and used by others who GlobalBX™ has no control over. 

We may also gather information as part of our analysis of use on our Site, such as which areas you visit and what services you access. This data enables us to become more familiar with which individuals visit our Site, how often they visit, and what parts of the Site are visited most often. There is information about your computer hardware and software that may be collected by GlobalBX™. This information can include without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses.

**Use of your Personal Information**

We use the information collected on our Site, whether personal, demographic, or technical for the purpose of operating and improving our Site. Information we collect is also used to customize your experience on our Site. We may use this information to alert you to products and services available from GlobalBX™ or from our affiliated companies. We would not disclose to a third party the fact that your business has been advertised for sale, other than displaying your advertisement on our website as well as on any affiliated partner sites that we choose.

We will not disclose your personal, demographic information, or information about your site usage to third parties except as set forth in this section of the Privacy Policy. We may disclose such information to companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf, such as hosting our web servers, analyzing data, and providing marketing assistance and customer service. These companies will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions but will not share that information to a third party. If legally required to disclose such information, we will do so if requested by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; protect the rights of property of GlobalBX™ or its affiliated companies; prevent a crime or protect national security; or protect the personal safety of users or the public. We may disclose such information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of GlobalBX™'s business.

We may contact you via e-mail or other means of communication to provide you with information about GlobalBX™'s products and services, updates regarding the GlobalBX™ website, such as additional listings which may be of interest to you. To provide you with co-branded services, we may share your information with our partners. If you prefer to not receive such information, you can let us know at the time you become a Registered User. You may also edit your user information at a later time. However, GlobalBX™ reserves the right to limit Registered Users to those who provide the requested information and accept our terms and condition of use and legal disclaimer as well as our privacy policy.

**Control and Access to your Personal Information**

You may at any time view, update, edit or delete the information you have provided to GlobalBX™ by accessing the User Registration page and following the instructions accordingly. If you delete some information, it may continue to be stored for archival purposes.

**Security of your Personal Information**

GlobalBX™ has implemented reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies designed to secure all our transactions and personal information from accidental loss and unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. We install firewalls and use password protection and encryption techniques where appropriate. While we endeavor to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us. 

**Use of Cookies**

GlobalBX™ uses "cookies" to help customize and maximize your online experience. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer nor is it used to retrieve any information about you from your computer that you have not voluntarily given to us. Cookies are a time saving feature used to submit your requests. Through the use of our cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. When you return to the GlobalBX™ site, the information you had provided previously can be retrieved so you can easily use the features you customized. You may also receive cookies when you link to our partners' sites or when you click on banner ads provided on our Site. You could edit your browser to accept or decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, the features of our Site may not function properly and negatively impact your experience on our Site.
